{
    "id": "a373078de2e8490bb8df7b55978b92d6",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have invited them ………………………….. lunch.",
            "description": "You invite people to an event. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03890af1450c49508dabede115f4433c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are not supposed to park …………………………… double yellow lanes.",
            "description": "Use on to indicate position on the surface. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81740847d2e54b4db171ec66ddd4fc88"
        },
        {
            "question": "She took some money ………………………….. her wallet.",
            "description": "Out of is the opposite of into.",
            "answers": [
                "out of",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d069d6ac7b543158a6096a6fe74b802"
        },
        {
            "question": "The people in my office are all easy to get ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by with",
                "on",
                "on with",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bcc87e6d202140228847cfe050ab026c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take that stupid smile ……………………………. your face.",
            "description": "To take something off is to remove it. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "65b8c34d32bb4a26a1091a2dec0758b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were remains of the meal all ………………………….. the floor.",
            "description": "All over means everywhere. ",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "77ab4a115d4042ebb3f5b6f86bc76085"
        },
        {
            "question": "The road goes …………………………….. a steep hill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "84d55854c3da4627a64ad02dca42793d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You know that girl …………………………. a brother who plays the piano?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24edebfc74c84e238124b221cb77aa31"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am quite pleased …………………………….. myself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0939d077e3e94d229d6d2681e4112f3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She suffers …………………………….. an incurable disease.",
            "description": "People suffer from illnesses. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "93fb0ae53954466b86e7ba128c2c1cbe"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is wrong ……………………………… you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9841adf472f740888ec65891cd2f4a9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you always yelling ……………………………… me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc6cd52559d64c6fb144804814931dfa"
        }
    ]
}